A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Staff FA487
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Staff
1913-1974
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
Rockefeller Foundation. International Health Board
Rockefeller Foundation. International Health Division
Rockefeller Foundation. China Medical Board
FA487
64.39 Cubic Feet 133 containers
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 20 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
File Plan
All material in this collection has not been assigned to a record group within the Rockefeller Foundation archives.
Scope and Contents
Contains reports, surveys and collected papers from Field Staff of the Rockefeller Foundation, International Health Board/Division, and China Medical Board. Also includes a selection of Officers Actions, Minutes, Board and Program reports and publications.
Arrangement
Arranged in 6 series primarily by Commission/Board, and file type.
- Laboratory Records of West African Yellow Fever Commission, 1; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 record storage boxes
  - African Monkey Books, 1-9. (Box 7)
  - African Monkey Books, 10-14 (Box 7A)
  - African Monkey Books, 15-24. (Box 7B)
  - Packages 4 and 5. (Box 7B)
  - African Monkey Books, 25-34. (Box 7C)
  - Packages 6 and 7. (Box 7C)
  - Protection Test Books, 1-8 (Box 7D)
  - Packages 8-9 (Box 7D)
  - Mosquito Books, 1-7 (Box 7E)
  - Mosquito Books, Packages 10-11 (Box 7E)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7E)
- International Health Board/Division (IHB/D), 2; 27.68 Cubic Feet 9 card file boxes (3x5), 11 record storage boxes, 30 letter document boxes, and 1 tall legal box.
  - International Health Division (IHD) - Officers' Actions, 2.1
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1929 (Box CIHD 4)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1930 (Box CIHD 4)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1931 (Box CIHD 4)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1932 (Box CIHD 4)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1933 (Box CIHD 4)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1934 (Box CIHD 5)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1935 (Box CIHD 5)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1936 (Box CIHD 5)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1937 (Box CIHD 5)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1938-1939 (Box CIHD 5)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1940-1941 (Box CIHD 6)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1942-1943 (Box CIHD 6)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1944 (Box CIHD 6)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1945 (Box CIHD 6)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1946 (Box CIHD 6)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1947 (Box CIHD 6)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1948 (Box CIHD 7)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1949 (Box CIHD 7)
    - IHD Officers' Actions, 1950 (Box CIHD 7)
  - International Health Board/Division (IHB/D) - Reports, 2.2
    - Reports 724-7419 (Box IHB/D 1)
      Scope and Contents note
      Incomplete
    - Reports 7424-7695 (Box IHB/D 2)
  - International Health Division (IHD) - Field Staff, 2.3
    - Salaries, Travel, Commutation, 1916-1922 (Box CIHD 1)
    - Salaries, Travel, Commutation, 1923-1924 (Box CIHD 1)
    - IHD Field Staff, 1926-1928 (Box CIHD 2)
    - IHD Field Staff, 1929-1931 (Box CIHD 2)
    - IHD Expenditures, 1913-1915 (Box CIHD 3)
    - IHD Expenditures, 1930-1941 (Box CIHD 3)
    - IHD Laboratory, 1941-1948 (Box CIHD 3)
    - IHD Laboratory, 1949-1952 (Box CIHD 3)
    - IHD Annual and Miscellaneous Reports (Box CIHD 8)
    - IHD Fellowships, 3 volumes. (Box CIHD 9)
    - IHD Field Staff, 1941-1946 (Box CIHD 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1941-1947; 2 volumes. (Box CIHD 9)
  - International Health Board (IHB) - Spanish, 2.4
    - Junta de Sanidad Internacional, 1915 (Box 1)
    - Junta de Sanidad Internacional, 1921 (Box 1)
    - Junta de Sanidad Internacional, 1922 (Box 1)
    - Junta de Sanidad Internacional, 1923 (Box 1)
    - Junta de Sanidad Internacional, 1924 (Box 1)
    - Junta de Sanidad Internacional, 1925 (Box 1)
    - Junta de Sanidad Internacional, 1926 (Box 1)
  - International Health Board (IHB) - Bulletin, 2.5
    - IHB Bulletin, Vol. 1-4, 1920-1924 (Box 2)
    - IHB Bulletin, Vol 5-6, 1924-1926 (Box 2)
    - IHB Bulletin, Vol. 7, 1926-1927 (Box 2)
  - International Health Division (IHD) - Newsletter, 2.6
    - IHD Newsletter, 1937-1938 (Box 3)
    - IHD Newsletter, 1939-1940 (Box 3)
    - IHD Newsletter, 1941-1950 (Box 4)
  - International Health Board/Division (IHB/D) - Minutes and Documents of Record, 2.7
    - IHB Minutes - Vol 1, 1913-1915 (Box 5)
    - IHB Minutes - Vol 2, 1916-1917 (Box 5)
    - IHB Minutes - Vol 3, 1918-1919 (Box 5)
    - IHB Minutes - Vol 4, 1920-1921 (Box 6)
    - IHB Minutes - Vol 5, 1922 (Box 6)
    - IHB Minutes - Vol 6, 1924 (Box 7)
    - IHB Minutes - Vol 7, 1925 (Box 7)
    - IHB Minutes - Vol 8, 1926 (Box 8)
    - IHB/CMB Minutes, 1916-1922 (Box 8)
    - IHB Documents of Record - Vol. I, 1913-1915 (Box 9)
    - IHB Documents of Record - Vol. II, 1916 (Box 9)
    - IHB Documents of Record - Vol. VII, 1921 (Box 9)
    - IHB Documents of Record - Vol. VIII, 1922 (Box 10)
    - IHB Documents of Record - Vol. IX, 1923 (Box 10)
    - IHB Documents of Record - Vol. X, 1924 (Box 10)
    - IHB Documents of Record - Vol. XI, 1925 (Box 10)
    - IHB Documents of Record - Vol. XII, 1926-1927 (Box 10)
    - IHB Financial Reports, 1914-1918; 1 volume. (Box 11)
    - IHB/CMB Minutes, 1919 (Box 11)
    - IHB/CMB Minutes, 1920 (Box 12)
    - IHB/CMB Minutes, 1921 (Box 12)
    - IHB/CMB Minutes, 1922 (Box 13)
    - IHB/CMB Minutes, 1923 (Box 13)
    - IHB/CMB/PUMC Minutes, 1924 (Box 14)
    - IHB/CMB/PUMC Minutes, 1925 (Box 15)
    - IHB/CMB/PUMC Minutes, 1926-1927; 1 volume. (Box 16)
    - IHD Minutes, 1929 (Box 17)
    - IHD Minutes, 1930 (Box 18)
    - IHD Minutes, 1931 (Box 19)
    - IHD Minutes, 1932 (Box 20)
    - IHD Minutes, 1933 (Box 20)
    - IHD Minutes, 1934 (Box 21)
    - IHD Minutes, 1935 (Box 21)
    - IHD Minutes, 1936 (Box 22)
    - IHD Minutes, 1937 (Box 22)
    - IHD Minutes, 1938 (Box 23)
    - IHD Minutes, 1939 (Box 23)
    - International Health Board/Division (IHB/D) Minutes Index, 9 box(es) 3.5x5x12 inches each.
      Scope and Contents
      The index includes entries for personal names, organizations, and countries or regions; but not subject terms. Citations to the IHB/D's minutes appear on the right edge of the cards as a 5-digit number, composed of the year and page number. For instance: "25123" = 1925, page 123.
      General
      Provides indexing to the International Health Board/Division's (IHB/D) minutes.
      Arrangement
      The index is arranged alphabetically.
      - A - B (Box 1)
      - C - DEL (Box 2)
      - DEM - GO (Box 3)
      - GR - J (Box 4)
      - K - ME (Box 5)
      - MI - PHY (Box 6)
      - PI - SM (Box 7)
      - SN - VE (Box 8)
      - VI - Z (Box 9)
  - IHB/D - Annual Reports, 2.8
    - 1915 (Box 24)
    - 1916 (Box 24)
    - 1918 (Box 24)
    - 1919 (Box 24)
    - 1920 (Box 24)
    - 1921 (Box 24)
    - 1922 (Box 24)
    - 1923 (Box 25)
    - 1924 (Box 25)
    - 1925 (Box 25)
    - 1926 (Box 25)
    - 1934 (Box 25)
    - 1935 (Box 25)
    - 1936 (Box 26)
    - 1937 (Box 26)
    - 1938 (Box 26)
    - 1939 (Box 26)
    - 1940 (Box 27)
    - 1941 (Box 27)
    - 1942 (Box 27)
    - 1943 (Box 27)
    - 1944 (Box 27)
    - 1945 (Box 27)
    - 1946 (Box 27)
    - 1947 (Box 27)
    - 1948 (Box 27)
    - 1949 (Box 27)
    - 1950 (Box 27)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1915 (Box 28)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1916 (Box 28)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1917 (Box 28)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1918 (Box 29)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1919 (Box 29)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1920 (Box 29)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1921 (Box 30)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1922 (Box 30)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1923 (Box 30)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1924 (Box 30)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1925 (Box 31)
    - IHB Annual Reports - Costa Rica, 1926 (Box 31)
- Rockefeller Foundation Health Commission, 3; 0.76 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation Health Commission, Vol. 1-3, 1940-1943; 2 copies. (Box 31, Box 32)
  - International Health Commission - Minutes, 1913 June-1915 (Box 32)
- Field Staff - Collected papers, 4; 11.39 Cubic Feet 30 letter document boxes
  - IHD Field Staff, 4.1
    - Index, 1924-1943; 2 copies. (Box 32)
    - Index, 1944-1950; 2 copies. (Box 32)
    - Index, 1951-1957 (Box 32)
    - Vol. I, 1924 (Box 33)
    - Vol. II, 1925 (Box 33)
    - Vol. III, 1926 (Box 33)
    - Vol. IV, 1927 (Box 34)
    - Vol. V, 1928 (Box 34)
    - Vol. VI, 1929 (Box 35)
    - Vol. VII, 1930 (Box 35)
    - Vol. VIII, Part 1 - A-K, 1931 (Box 36)
    - Vol. VIII, Part 2 - M-Z, 1931 (Box 36)
    - Vol. IX, Part 1 - A-K, 1932 (Box 37)
    - Vol. IX, Part 2 - L-Z, 1932 (Box 37)
    - Vol. X, Part 1 - A-L, 1933 (Box 38)
    - Vol. X, Part 2 - M-Z, 1933 (Box 38)
    - Vol. XI, Part 1 - A-M, 1934 (Box 39)
    - Vol. XI, Part 2 - N-Z, 1934 (Box 39)
    - Vol. XII, Part 1 - A-K, 1935 (Box 40)
    - Vol. XII, Part 2 - L-Z, 1935 (Box 40)
    - Vol. XIII, Part 1 - A-K, 1936 (Box 41)
    - Vol. XIII, Part 2 - L-Z, 1936 (Box 41)
    - Vol. XIV, Part 1 - A-R, 1937 (Box 42)
    - Vol. XIV, Part 2 - S-Z, 1937 (Box 42)
    - Vol. XV, Part 1 - A-K, 1938 (Box 43)
    - Vol. XV, Part 2 - L-Z, 1938 (Box 43)
    - Vol. XVI, Part 1 - A-K, 1939 (Box 44)
    - Vol. XVI, Part 2 - L-Z, 1939 (Box 44)
    - Vol. XVII, Part 1 - A-K, 1940 (Box 44)
    - Vol. XVIII, Part 1 - A-J, 1941 (Box 45)
    - Vol. XVIII, Part 2 - K-Z, 1941 (Box 46)
    - Vol. XIX, Part 1 - A-L, 1942 (Box 46)
    - Vol. XIX, Part 2 - M-Z, 1942 (Box 47)
    - Vol. XX, Part 1 - A-K, 1943 (Box 47)
    - Vol. XX, Part 2 - L-Z, 1943 (Box 48)
    - Vol. XXI, Part 1 - A-K, 1944 (Box 48)
    - Vol. XXI, Part 2 - L-Z, 1944 (Box 49)
    - Vol. XXII, Part 1 - A-G, 1945 (Box 49)
    - Vol. XXII, Part 2 - H-Z, 1945 (Box 49)
    - Vol. XXIII, 1946 (Box 50)
    - Vol. XXIV, 1947 (Box 50)
    - Vol. XXV, 1948 (Box 51)
    - Vol. XXVI, 1949 (Box 50)
    - Vol. XXVII, 1950 (Box 52)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Division of Medicine and Public Health, 4.2
    - Vol. XXVIII, 1951 (Box 52)
    - Vol. XXIX, 1952 (Box 52)
    - Vol. XXX, 1953 (Box 53)
    - Vol. XXXI, 1954-1955 (Box 53)
    - Vol. XXXII, 1956-1957 (Box 53)
    - Vol. XXXIII, 1958 (Box 54)
    - Vol. XXXIV, 1959 (Box 54)
    - Vol. XXXV, 1960 (Box 54)
    - Vol. XXXVI, 1961 (Box 54)
    - Vol. XXXVII, 1962 (Box 55)
    - Vol. XXXVIII, 1963 (Box 55)
    - Vol. XXXVIX, 1964 (Box 55)
    - Vol. XL, 1965 (Box 55)
    - Vol. XLI, 1966 (Box 56)
    - Vol. XLII, 1967 (Box 56)
    - Vol. XLIII, 1968 (Box 56)
  - IHD - Collected Papers on Yellow Fever, 4.3
    - Vol. I (Box 57)
    - Vol. II (Box 57)
    - Vol. III (Box 58)
    - Vol. IV (Box 58)
    - Vol. V (Box 59)
    - Vol. VI (Box 59)
    - Vol. VII (Box 60)
    - Vol. VIII (Box 60)
    - Vol. IX (Box 61)
- Rockefeller Foundation War Relief Commission, 5; 0.38 Cubic Feet 1 letter document box
  - Rockefeller Foundation War Relief Commission Reports, 2 volumes. (Box 61)
- Rockefeller Foundation Program Reports, 6; 17.44 Cubic Feet 44 letter document boxes, 1 letter document box (wide) and 1 half-letter document box
  - Mexican Agricultural Program, 6.1
    - Folleto Miscelaneo. Vol. 1-3 (Box 62)
    - Folleto Miscelaneo. Vol. 4 (Box 62)
    - Folleto Miscelaneo. Vol. 5-6 (Box 62)
    - Folleto de Divulgacion, Vol. 1-9 (Box 63)
    - Folleto de Divulgacion, Vol. 10-11 (Box 63)
    - Folleto de Divulgacion, Vol. 12-20 (Box 63)
    - Folleto Technico, Vol. 1-10 (Box 63)
    - Folleto Technico, Vol. 11-20 (Box 64)
    - Folleto Technico, Vol. 21-30 (Box 64)
  - RF Field Staff Reports, Surveys and Papers (Blue Volumes), 6.2
    - 1 - Ankylostomiasis (Box 64)
    - 2 - General Public Health (Box 65)
    - 3 - Public Health Administraiton (Box 65)
    - 4 - Annual Report (Box 65)
    - 5 - Preliminary Report (Box 66)
    - 6 - Use of Fish (Box 66)
    - 8 - Conference (Box 66)
    - 9 - Abstracts, 1921-1922 (Box 66)
    - 10 - Abstracts, 1925-1926 (Box 67)
    - 11 - Southern States, Vol. 1, 1915-1917 (Box 67)
    - 12 - Southern States, Vol. 1, 1918-1919 (Box 67)
    - 14 - Tab Summary, Vol. 3, 1914-1917 (Box 68)
    - 15 - Tab Summary, Vol. 3, 1918-1919 (Box 68)
    - 16 - Tab Summary, Vol. 1, A, 1914-1919 (Box 68)
    - 17 - Tab Summary, Vol 1, B, 1914-1919 (Box 69)
    - 18 - Yellow Fever, Vol. 1 (Box 69)
    - 20 - Tab Summary, Vol. 2, A, 1914-1919 (Box 70)
    - 21 - Tab Summary, Vol. 2, B, 1914-1919 (Box 70)
    - 22 - Deaths Following Treatment, Vol. 1 (Box 70)
    - 23 - Deaths Following Treatment, Vol. 2 (Box 71)
    - 24 - Public Health Nurse (Box 71)
    - 25 - Bibliography of Carbon (Box 71)
    - 27 - Deaths Following Treatment, Vol. 1, 1915-1934 (Box 72)
    - 28 - Deaths Following Treatment, Vol. 2, 1915-1934 (Box 72)
    - 29 - Report on Health Agencies (Box 72)
    - 30 - Deaths Following Treatment, Vol. 1, 1922-1933 (Box 73)
    - 31 - Deaths Following Treatment, Vol. 2, 1922-1933 (Box 73)
    - 32 - Form 49, Vol. 2 A, 1915-1919 (Box 73)
    - 33 - Form 49, Vol. 2 B, 1915-1919 (Box 74)
    - 34 - Yellow Fever Commission (Box 74)
    - 35 - Intensive Community Work (Box 74)
    - 36 - Work in Trinidad and Tobago, Vol. 1 (Box 75)
    - 37 - Work in Trinidad and Tobago, Vol. 2 (Box 75)
    - 38 - Report on Uncinariasis (Box 75)
    - 39 - Resurvey on Hookworm (Box 75)
    - 40 - Notes on Vermifuge Treatment (Box 76)
    - 41 - Minutes of Meetings (Box 76)
    - 42 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, A (Box 76)
    - 43 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, B (Box 77)
    - 44 - Eradication of Ankylostomiasis (Box 77)
    - 46 - Clinical Manifestation of Yellow Fever (Box 77)
    - 47 - Malay Report (Box 78)
    - 48 - Republic of Haiti (Box 78)
    - 49 - Survey of Haiti (Box 78)
    - 50 - Schedule #3 (Box 78)
    - 51 - Officers in Training, Vol. 2 A (Box 79)
    - 52 - Officers in Training, Vol. 2 B (Box 79)
    - 53 - Officers in Training, Vol. 1 A (Box 80)
    - 54 - Officers in Training, Vol. 1 B (Box 80)
    - 55 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, Vol. 1 A (Box 80)
    - 56 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, Vol. 1 B (Box 81)
    - 57 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, Vol. 2 A (Box 81)
    - 58 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, Vol. 2 B (Box 81)
    - 59 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, Vol. 2 C (Box 82)
    - 60 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, Vol. 4 A (Box 82)
    - 61 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, Vol. 4 B (Box 82)
    - 62 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, Vol. 3 A (Box 83)
    - 63 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, Vol. 3 B (Box 83)
    - 64 - Australian Hookworm Campaign, Vol. 3 C (Box 83)
    - 76 - Feasibility of Controlling Malaria, Part 1 (Box 84)
    - 77 - Feasibility of Controlling Malaria, Part 2 (Box 84)
    - 78 - Malaria Surveys of Puerto Rico (Box 84)
    - 79 - Co-Op Work in North Carolina (Box 85)
    - 80 - Anopheles Mosquito Reduction (Box 85)
    - 81 - Preliminary Report on Anopheles Mosquito (Box 85)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Charter and Bylaws, 1916-1955; 1 volume (Box 86)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Charter and Bylaws, 1963; 1 pamphlet (Box 86)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Charter and Bylaws, 1966; 1 pamphlet (Box 86)
  - Inter-Asian Corn Improvement Program (IACP) Workshop, 1966-1974; Multiple volumes for each year. (Box 86, Box 87, Box 88)
  - Thailand National Corn and Sorghum Program Annual Report, 1970-1974; 1976; 1 volume for each year. (Box 88, Box 89)
  - Conquest of Hunger Symposium, 1 volume. (Box 89)
  - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) Annual Report, 1963 (Box 90)
  - "Agricultural Credit and Finance in Africa", by Miller, L.F. (Box 90)
  - Agricultural Program of the Rockefeller Foundation, 1956 (Box 90)
  - Indian Agricultural Program, 1959 (Box 91)
  - Agricultural Journal Series papers, 1-136 (Box 90)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1953-1954 (Box 91)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1954-1955 (Box 91)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1955-1956 (Box 92)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1956-1957 (Box 92)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1957-1958 (Box 93)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1958-1959 (Box 94)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1959-1960 (Box 94)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box 94)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1961-1962 (Box 94)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1962-1963 (Box 95)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1963-1964 (Box 95)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1964-1965 (Box 95)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Agricultural Sciences Annual Report, 1965-1966 (Box 95)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Trustee - Program Review Committee - Interim Report, 1973 April 4; 1 volume (Box 95A)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Trustee - Program Review Committee - Second Interim Report, 1973 September 19; 1 volume (Box 95A)
  - Rockefeller Foundation Trustee - Program Review Committee - Final Report, 1973 December 3 (Box 95A)
  - Agricultural Program Annual Reports - Chile, 1955-1959; 4 volumes. (Box 96)
  - Agricultural Program Annual Reports - Colombia, 1954-1959; 10 volumes including copies. (Box 96, Box 97)
  - A Proposal for the Reorganization of International Maize + Wheat Center (Box 96)
  - Agricultural Program Annual Reports - Mexico, 1954-1959; 7 volumes. (Box 97, Box 98)
  - Agricultural Program Annual Reports - India, 1957-1959; 3 volumes. (Box 99)
  - Virus Laboratories Annual Reports - Belem, Brazil, 1960-1969; 11 volumes. (Box 99, Box 100)
  - Virus Laboratories Annual Reports - Cali, Colombia, 1964-1969; 4 volumes. (Box 100)
  - Virus Laboratories Annual Reports - Ibadan, Nigeria, 1964-1971; 8 volumes. (Box 101)
  - Virus Laboratories Annual Reports - New Haven, CT (Yale University), 1965-1972; 8 volumes. (Box 102, Box 103)
  - Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research, 1957 Annual Report (Box 103)
  - Virus Laboratories Annual Reports - Poona Virus Research Center, 1961-1971; 13 volumes including copies. (Box 104, Box 105)
  - Virus Laboratories Annual Reports - Port-of-Spain, Trinidad, 1960-1967, 1973; 8 volumes. (Box 105, Box 106)
  - Medical Education in Asia: A Symposium, China Medical Board
  - "Measurement and Management in Medicine and Health Services", by John. R. Evans (Box 106)